Hello?
Dean, are you ready?
Dean, 你准备好了吗?
I'll be right down.
我马上就下来.
Don't worry. We have plenty of time.
不用担心. 我们有足够的时间.
Hi.
嗨!
The train to New York doesn't leave till 1:30 or so.
去纽约的火车不会离开 直到1:30左右.
Let's see.
我们看看.
Do you mean the 1:25?
你的意思是1:25这趟?
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, 就是这个.
Kevin, that's a local. See?
Kevin, 那是趟慢车. 看?
It's in blue.
它是用蓝色标记的.
It stops everywhere.
它到处停.
It arrives in New York at 7:39 tonight!
它到纽约 在今晚的7:39!
Well, we don't want that.
Well, 我们不想要那个.
Is there an express?
有快车吗?
I see. They're in red.
我看到了. 它们是红色的.
The next one leaves at 1:10. Damn!
下一趟1:10离开. Damn!
-When's the next train after that? -4:15.
-那趟车之后的下一趟什么时候呢? -4:15
It's not there.
它不在那儿.
The 1:10?
1:10开的那趟?
It's got a symbol beside it. A square.
它有一个标记在它旁边. 一个正方形.
What does that mean?
那是什么意思?
This train does not run on weekends.
这趟火车周末不开.